ظآزI defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortalityظآز
ظآزAt last you say
we've been apart too longظآز
ظآزUnwilling, unyielding, I won't let goظآز
ظآزWith you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a streamظآز
ظآزIf heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vesselظآز
ظآزIf it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Daoظآز
ظآزEven if countless stars
turn into my foesظآز
ظآزTo grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long nightظآز
=Rise Again=
=Episode 22=
Ningxue!
So all these ten thousand years,
you've been trapped here.
Ningxue!
Ningxue.
Don't worry.
I will get you out of here.
(Ten Thousand Years Ago)
It's been ages since the Immortal Realm
looked this beautiful.
That curse on you is fierce.
but I've infused you
a breath of my spiritual energy.
It should buy you
three hundred more years.
Ningxue,
I'm going into seclusion now.
I hope to break into
the Heavenly God Realm
by then,
and lift this curse for you.
But all I want is for you to be safe.
Even if the Heavenly Dao descends...
I won't
let anyone take you from me.
I have one last wish.
Ningxue.
Ningxue!
No.
That demon remnant
triggered the curse early.
Ningxue, I'm not leaving you.
Ningxue...
Ningxue!
Hang in there.
I'll get you out.
Ningxue.
How are you feeling?
My Lord, the Holy Maiden..
Ningxue!
Ningxue.
Su Wubing.
You're finally awake.
I remember now.
I remember everything.
So
much time has passed.
That's great.
Your curse is finally broken.
But won't that draw the Heavenly Dao?
Maybe it hasn't noticed yet.
Or...
My Lord,
we should leave now.
Let's go.
This...?
ظآزI defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortalityظآز
ظآزAt last you say
we've been apart too longظآز
ظآزUnwilling, unyielding, I won't let goظآز
ظآزWith you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a streamظآز
ظآزIf heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vesselظآز
ظآزIf it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Daoظآز
ظآزEven if countless stars
turn into my foesظآز
ظآزTo grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long nightظآز